day delivery
Pharmacy.
how are you sir
quiet?
what is your name?
Adilson,
Adilson.
what is the name of this street?
here is Holy Spirit.
I'm waiting for a delivery,
but it's not pharmacy.
it's not the pharmacy, no.
it's not pharmacy
it says here
anxiety and stress remedy.
no,
this is not where they asked,
no.
what is your name?
Adilson,
Adilson, is.
the name is usually here,
Probably here for us.
Adilson, is.
It's okay, man,
is four gods from this
for you to take every three hours.
is the gourmetiro
it's the creative way I use to be able to sell
and vice versa.
that's why I pranked you.
then I just got the street name wrong.
and I'm a diabetes,
I can't, boy.
but we don't charge anything for the product,
saw?
only the delivery fee,
twelve reais.
ok,
thanks.
Great day for you,
man.
but the beach is turning,
yeah
To turn. it was worth.
great day there!